A horror icon is reborn.
Leprechaun: Origins is a horror film directed by Zach Lipovsky.
Two young couples backpacking through Ireland discover that one of
Ireland's most famous legends is a terrifying reality.
Sophie, played by Stephanie Bennett.
Ben, played by Andrew Dunbar.
Jeni, played by Melissa Roxburgh.
David, played by Brendan Fletcher.
Hamish, played by Garry Chalk.
Sean, played by Teach Grant.
Leprechaun: Origins is a 2014 American horror film directed by Zach Lipovsky, written by Harris Wilkinson and starring Dylan Postl (better
known by his wrestling ring name Hornswoggle), with Melissa Roxburgh, Garry Chalk, and Brendan Fletcher co-starring in the film.
It is a reboot of Leprechaun (1993) and the seventh
installment in the Leprechaun franchise.
WWE Studios President Michael Luisi has described the film as "a little darker, a little
more traditional horror than the Warwick Davis ones that people remember".
The film was released to select theaters on August 22, 2014, followed by
VOD on 26 August and a DVD/Blu-ray release on September 30.
The film was panned by critics and fans upon release.
The film explores themes of northern ireland, leprechaun, prequel.
The tone is dark.